hey everyone this is the inside of the
comma office is any over here at the
firm where station and he's bringing off
the new neo right here we are going to
be using this neo and putting it in our
new car
remember those secrets on the whiteboard
what Shh didn't want to be periscope
welcome it's their first day on
periscope so we're bringing up a board
and as you know when you flash your neo
you have to press down the button hey
Peter bench there you go you can say
that it's running a giant panda panda
Japan to carry your board for your knee
oh yeah we're gonna plug in you found it
right angle us me yep good cable cool so
I've already flashed neo ass an open
pilot on that Neil and we're gonna take
it out to our new car and that's what
we're going to be announcing today right
here on periscope actually put the
heatsink so cool let's walk back to the
Calvi this is the Khmer I advanced lab
for building the innovation you see it's
like uh may i
and it's max car
I can't tell if that's a smiley face or
a frowny face because the words are
upside-down well why isn't oh I don't
have to unlock orientation what that up
we're putting in the heat sinks into
this on to the 1 plus this is a 1 plus
3t GoPro mount that one prepared so
we're not going to be replacing the rear
view mirror of this car we're gonna be
using the GoPro mount which is also
available in the neo repository this is
a GoPro mount and a GoPro mount new your
adapter already got oh and also the key
to our car yeah the big reveal maybe we
got to get in over a hundred people into
this periscope isn't that what Martin
shkreli does before it does big reveals
you usually expensive sauna this is are
no longer oh this is are no longer
expensive soldering iron alright cool
Hey oh yeah yeah wait what about the
sign okay as close we have to sign
things some people remind me that we're
a real company around here it's still oh
really believe it you're a Ford Fiesta
has electronic steering assistance yes I
do think you could make the steering
wheel move oh yeah without touching it
of course um I think what you're gonna
have to do is figure out how the car is
moving it you're gonna want to sniff the
can bus a great way to do that is with a
comma AI panda which right now you can
only win so go on our forms and make our
three new moderators happy and you can
win a panda so yeah can we get a hundred
people in here hundred people will be
sweet like yeah I know no place still
looks the same
yeah not much has changed you know
[Music]
DoubleTap to flip camera hey how's it
going periscope 34 lookout 33 come on
come on let's get some people Oh invited
followers now we're talking I didn't
realize you could do that but I like
that
that's alright yeah you got your cover
on so just doing neo assembly here
getting the newest neo together
let's also grab its serial number baby
and put a label on it
oh yeah invites slack how am I not doing
that doing that channel that's a thing
yeah get slack over here on periscope
let's get 100 people will do the reveal
of our new car okay this is the logitech
mount this is the number one mouth that
we recommend and I can stick it right
here on my phone yeah that's that's
that's pretty good the best $40 buy one
of these logitech mounts there they're
like the best mount you can get for
Scheffer they're not perfectly rigid
they could be made a little bit more
rigid but they're a lot better than some
of the other mounts we see on the
suction cup is this thing you can like
really torque it down with which is
pretty nice what's the best map for a
neo well for neo we used to replace the
rearview mirror and we had a slide in
thing but yeah if you want to do away
with that so this is what we have I can
show you here umm this is also available
in the new your repository I do know the
open XC we could talk about that in a
minute but this is the GoPro mount
slider so then you can just buy GoPro
mounts off Amazon and it slides into the
same thing
it's almost as rigid as the rear view
mirror and you know you get to keep
now the kite what happens cut out too
much where's the new car well it's not
in here this is the basement
oh yeah the GoPro mounts are real cheap
oh yeah I've heard about the neck see if
you go look at the open XC documentation
they specifically say it can't do it
can't do the a lot of can if you
saturate the bus it won't be able to
keep up because it's doing like JSON
encoding on this tiny microprocessor oh
yes that is the giant panda board that
he installed in this new neo pandas are
way more powerful pandas are way more
powerful your neo board or your open XC
strip
oh of course yeah both the Panda and the
neo boards are both supported for open
pilot are we currently hiring people for
software engineer girls yes we are um
check out comma dot AI slash positions
it's linked to from the main page as
well so check that out if you like that
yeah you have to work with JSON like I
don't understand why they would do that
I mean what you should do is you should
have the micro controller output binary
protocol and then turn it into JSON if
you want your Python libraries which is
what the Panda library does so for those
who don't know Panda is our Universal
car interface and right now the only way
to get one is to win one by using our
App shipper and by being active on our
forms community.com dot a I if you
haven't seen our force alright alright
is the neo together neo is I heard I
heard about the tesla cannon' messages
Tesla key message scares me for steering
its controls to angle not torque and be
careful limit the fork limit torque will
have to make sure torque is limited on
our new
you need some help putting this on the
new car yeah put it on the new car with
this all right
few people can we get 50 people will
change it to 50 oh yeah any people um we
need people yeah
you gotta get right a little slack oh
just check the slack do we invite any
slack we're interested in all Road data
did someone go in the main forum do at
channel get on periscope yeah see if
anyone already did it get on the
periscope go ahead get on the periscope
oh yeah so do it yeah I know they wrote
it they do at channel yeah take a selfie
uh
what the ladder means but at channel
alerts the whole Channel come check out
show you the backyard
what about roads without painted lines
it kind of works um it works pretty well
everywhere uh as long as it looks like
things the machine learning models have
seen before um so yeah this is our
backyard let's wait until we get a few
people all 51 all right now we're
talking right so we added the channel on
slack nibble get some more
um but yeah for now who has questions
let's ask questions it's question
o'clock I remember last time this mostly
just turned into bashing the car
industry but um no the new car it's it's
non Honda and we're very excited about
it
it's yeah I like this company it's a
good company that makes a car that's
just not for you know 5758 alright now
we're getting some people in here I'm
liking this
alright let's go back to the Calvi let's
see how our neo is doing you're gonna
clean that cable up okay um what I
accept speed control with only excel and
regen no break for the bounty II maybe
the problem with that is not you need to
break because if your car battery is
full you can't do regenerate if the
reservoir is full yeah you can't know
the battery yeah cuz regen charges the
battery right if you're bad yeah if your
battery is full
camera orientation leave me by that
did I do something weird maybe it's the
periscope app being weird wow we're get
a lot of people in here alright I'm
liking this I headed the channel you're
out of the channel it's worth 60 people
in 19 different times oh wow so many
times on tonight
um so Eddie's gonna put together a cable
here and we're gonna use this table so
the way that we port to a new car is we
first sniff what the existing system is
doing um so this will be a great
periscope to watch and pay attention to
if you are interested in portent to
require yourself
so the first step lost the feed oh do I
not have good reception